<?xml version="1.0"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="drug-table.xslt"?><drug name = "asparaginase (L-asparaginase) inj VIAL">
<dose><value>25 000</value>
<value>12 500</value>
</dose>
<route><value>IM</value>
</route>
<strength><value>10 000 unit</value>
</strength>
<frequency><value>ONCE</value>
<value>WEEKLY</value>
</frequency>
<instruction><value>ONCE. (Day 5 of 28). Observe patient for 1 hour post Asparaginase dose.</value>
<value>WEEKLY on DAY 29, 36 and 43. Observe patient for 1 hour post asparaginase.</value>
<value>WEEKLY on DAY 1, 8 and 15. Observe patient for 1 hour post asparaginase. </value>
<value>WEEKLY on DAY 1, 8 and 15. Observe patient for 1 hour post asparaginase.</value>
</instruction>
<volume></volume>
<units><value>unit/m2</value>
</units>
<Population><value>ADULT</value>
</Population>
<IndicationPRN></IndicationPRN>
<AdditionalNotes><value>If fibrinogen is less than 1 g/L or Amylase is greater than or equal to 3 X WLN OR Lipase is greater than WLN: HOLD asparaginase. If fibrinogen is less than or equal to 0.5 g/L OR if fibrinogen is greater than 0.5 g/L AND symptomatic: Give 10 units of cryoprecipitate. Repeat fibrinogen daily until greater than 1 g/L. If mild to severe hypersensitivity reactions, switch to Erwina Asparaginase.</value>
<value>If abdominal pain present 72 hours or longer AND Amylase is greater than or equal to 3 X WLN: Permanently stop asparaginase. If abdominal pain present less than 72 hours AND Amylase less than 3 X WLN: HOLD asparaginase and resume when values return to baseline. If Amylase greater than or equal to 3 X WLN AND no abdominal pain: Check Lipase; if Lipase above normal: HOLD asparaginase. If Fibrinogen less than 1 g/L: HOLD asparaginase. If Fibrinogen is less than or equal to 0.5 g/L OR Fibrinogen is greater than 0.5 g/L and symptomatic: Give 10 units of cryoprecipitate. Repeat Fibrinogen daily until greater than 1 g/L. If mild to severe asparaginase hypersensitivity reactions: switch to Erwinia asparaginase.</value>
<value>If abdominal pain present 72 hours or longer AND Amylase is greater than or equal to 3 X WLN: Permanently stop asparaginase. If abdominal pain present less than 72 hours AND Amylase less than 3 X WLN: HOLD asparaginase and resume when values return to baseline. If Amylase greater than 3 X WLN AND no abdominal pain: Check Lipase; if Lipase above normal: HOLD asparaginase. If Fibrinogen less than 1 g/L: HOLD asparaginase. If Fibrinogen is less than or equal to 0.5 g/L OR Fibrinogen is greater than 0.5 g/L and symptomatic: Give 10 units of cryoprecipitate. Repeat Fibrinogen daily until greater than 1 g/L. If mild to severe asparaginase hypersensitivity reactions: switch to Erwinia asparaginase.</value>
</AdditionalNotes>
<BackgroundInformation><value>http://intraweb01.albertahealthservices.ca/Pharmacy/AHS_FORMULARY/search_details.aspx?id=3343</value>
</BackgroundInformation>
<PRNInformation></PRNInformation>
<AHSFormularyStatus></AHSFormularyStatus>
<HighAlert><value>HIGH ALERT MEDICATION</value>
</HighAlert>
</drug>