<?xml version="1.0"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="drug-table.xslt"?><drug name = "gemcitabine inj VIAL">
<dose><value>1000</value>
<value>1250</value>
<value>1200</value>
</dose>
<route><value>IV</value>
</route>
<strength><value>1 g</value>
<value>2 g</value>
<value>200 mg</value>
</strength>
<frequency><value>ONCE</value>
</frequency>
<instruction><value>DAY 1 of 21. Administer dose diluted in 0.9% sodium chloride 100 mL over 30 to 60 minutes. Administer concurrently with 250 to 500 mL 0.9% sodium chloride infusion.</value>
<value>DAY 8 of 21. Administer dose diluted in 0.9% sodium chloride 100 mL over 30 to 60 minutes. Administer concurrently with 250 to 500 mL 0.9% sodium chloride infusion.</value>
<value>DAY 1 of 21. Administer dose diluted in 0.9% sodium chloride 100 mL over 30 to 60 minutes. Start gemcitabine during pre-hydration.</value>
<value>DAY 8 of 21. Administer dose diluted in 0.9% sodium chloride 100 mL over 30 to 60 minutes. Administer concurrently with 0.9% sodium chloride infusion of 250 to 500 mL.</value>
<value>DAY 1 of 21. Administer dose diluted in 0.9% sodium chloride 100 mL over 30 to 60 minutes. Administer concurrently with 0.9% sodium chloride infusion of 250 to 500 mL.</value>
</instruction>
<volume><value>26.3 mL</value>
<value>52.6 mL</value>
<value>5.3 mL</value>
</volume>
<units><value>mg/m2</value>
</units>
<Population><value>Gemcitabine / CARBOplatin. Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer</value>
<value>Gemcitabine / CISplatin. Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer</value>
<value>Gemcitabine. Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer</value>
</Population>
<IndicationPRN></IndicationPRN>
<AdditionalNotes><value>If ANC is greater than or equal to 1.5 AND Plts are greater than or equal to 100 x 109/L: Give as ordered. If ANC is less than 1.5 OR Plts are less than 100 x 109/L: Delay 1 week.</value>
<value>If ANC is greater than 1 AND Plts are greater than 100 x 109/L: Give as ordered. If ANC is greater than or equal to 0.5 and less than or equal to 1 OR Plts are greater than  75 and less than or equal to 100 x 109/L: Give 75% of gemcitabine dose. If ANC is less than 0.5 OR Plts are less than or equal to 75 x 109/L: Delay 1 week.</value>
<value>If ANC is greater than or equal to 1.5 AND Plts are greater than or equal to 100 x 109/L: Give as ordered. If ANC is less than 1.5 OR Plts are less than 100 x 109/L: Delay 1 week. If calculated CrCl is greater than or equal to 50 mL/minute: give chemotherapy as ordered. If calculated CrCl is less than 50 mL/minute: Delay 1 week.</value>
<value>If ANC is greater than 1 AND Plts are greater than 100 x 109/L: Give as ordered. If ANC is greater than or equal to 0.5 and less than or equal to 1 OR Plts are greater than  75 and less than or equal to 100 x 109/L: Give 75% of gemcitabine dose. If ANC is less than 0.5 OR Plts are less than or equal to 75 x 109/L: Hold treatment.</value>
</AdditionalNotes>
<BackgroundInformation><value>http://intraweb01.albertahealthservices.ca/Pharmacy/AHS_FORMULARY/search_details.aspx?id=3329</value>
<value>http://intraweb01.albertahealthservices.ca/Pharmacy/AHS_FORMULARY/search_details.aspx?id=3330</value>
<value>http://intraweb01.albertahealthservices.ca/Pharmacy/AHS_FORMULARY/search_details.aspx?id=3328</value>
</BackgroundInformation>
<PRNInformation></PRNInformation>
<AHSFormularyStatus></AHSFormularyStatus>
<HighAlert><value>HIGH ALERT MEDICATION</value>
</HighAlert>
</drug>