<?xml version="1.0"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../../web/xslt/drug-table.xslt"?><drug name = "CISplatin inj VIAL">
<dose><value>50</value>
<value>75</value>
<value>80</value>
<value>25</value>
</dose><route><value>IV</value>
</route><form><value>inj VIAL</value>
</form><drugname><value>CISplatin inj VIAL</value>
</drugname><strength><value>1 mg/mL</value>
</strength><frequency><value>ONCE</value>
<value>DAILY</value>
</frequency><instruction><value>DAY 1. Administer dose diluted in 250 mL 0.9% sodium chloride over 1 hour concurrently with mannitol.</value>
<value>DAY 8. Administer dose diluted in 250 mL 0.9% sodium chloride over 1 hour concurrently with mannitol.</value>
<value>DAY 1 of 21. Administer dose diluted in 250 mL 0.9% sodium chloride over 1 hour concurrently with mannitol.</value>
<value>DAYS 1, 2 &amp; 3 of 21. Administer dose diluted in 250 mL 0.9% sodium chloride over 30 minutes, for 3 days.</value>
<value>DAY 1 of 28. Administer dose diluted in 250 mL 0.9% sodium chloride over 1 hour concurrently with mannitol on DAY 1 ONLY.</value>
<value>DAY 8 of 28. Administer dose diluted in 250 mL 0.9% sodium chloride over 1 hour concurrently with mannitol.</value>
</instruction><volume><value>100 mL</value>
<value>50 mL</value>
</volume><units><value>mg/m2</value>
<value>mg/m2/day</value>
</units><additionalnotes><value>DAY 1. If ANC greater than or equal to 1.5 AND Plts greater than or equal to 100 x 109/L, Give as ordered. If ANC less than 1.5 OR Plts less than 100 x 109/L: Delay one week. If CrCl is greater than or equal to 50 mL/minute, give chemotherapy as ordered. If CrCl less than 50 mL/minute,hold chemotherapy and contact physician.</value>
<value>DAY 8. If ANC greater than or equal to 1 AND Plts greater than or equal to 75 x 109/L, Give as ordered. If ANC is greater than 0.5 and less than 1 OR Plts are greater than 50 and less than 75 x 109/L: Administer 75% of vinorelbine dose. If ANC is less than or equal to 0.5 OR Plts are less than 50 x 109/L. HOLD treatment. If CrCl is greater than or equal to 50 mL/minute, give chemotherapy as ordered. If CrCl less than 50 mL/minute,hold chemotherapy and contact physician.</value>
<value>DAY 1. If ANC greater than or equal to 1.5 AND Plts greater than or equal to 100 x 109/L, Give as ordered. If ANC less than 1.5 OR Plts less than 100 x 109/L: Delay one week or adjust dose as per prescriber. If CrCl is greater than or equal to 50 mL/minute, give chemotherapy as ordered. If CrCl less than 50 mL/minute, hold chemotherapy and contact physician. If AST/ALT less than or equal to 1.5 x ULN and Alk Phos is less than 1.5 x ULN and bilirubin is WLN: Give as ordered. If AST/ALT greater than 1.5 to 5 x ULN AND Alk Phos 1.5 to 5 x ULN OR bilirubin ULN to 1.5 x ULN: Administer 75% of vinorelbine dose. If AST/ALT greater than 5 x ULN AND Alk Phos greater than 5 x ULN OR bilirubin greater than 1.5 x ULN: HOLD treatment. If vinorelbine held for hepatic toxicity, repeat liver function tests weekly. Once recovered, dose vinorelbine at 75%.</value>
<value>If ANC is greater than or equal to 1.5 AND Plts greater than or equal to 100 x 109/L AND Creatinine Clearance is greater than or equal to 45 mL/minute: Give as ordered. If ANC is less than 1.5 OR Plts are less than 100 x 109/L OR Creatinine Clearance is less than 45 mL/minute: Delay 1 week. NONHEMATOLOGIC TOXICITIES (dosage adjustment guidelines): Any Grade 3 or 4 toxicities (except mucositis): 75% pemetrexed &amp; 75% CISplatin dose. Any diarrhea requiring hospitalization or any: Grade 3 or 4 diarrhea: 75% pemetrexed and 75% CISplatin dose. Grade 3 or 4 mucositis: 50% pemetrexed and 100% CISplatin dose.</value>
<value>DAY 1. If ANC greater than or equal to 1.5 AND Plts greater than or equal to 100 x 109/L, Give as ordered. If ANC less than 1.5 OR Plts less than 100 x 109/L: Delay one week. If CrCl is greater than or equal to 50 mL/minute, give as ordered. If CrCl less than 50 mL/minute, hold chemotherapy and contact prescriber. If AST/ALT less than or equal to 1.5 x ULN and Alk Phos is less than 1.5 x ULN and bilirubin is WLN: Give as ordered. If AST/ALT greater than 1.5 to 5 x ULN AND Alk Phos is greater than or equal to 1.5 up to 5 x ULN OR bilirubin ULN to 1.5 x ULN: Administer 75% of vinorelbine dose. If AST/ALT greater than 5 x ULN AND Alk Phos greater than 5 x ULN OR bilirubin greater than 1.5 x ULN: HOLD treatment. If vinorelbine held for hepatic toxicity, repeat liver function tests weekly. Once recovered, dose vinorelbine at 75%.</value>
<value>DAY 1. If ANC greater than or equal to 1.5 AND Plts greater than or equal to 100 x 109/L, Give as ordered. If ANC less than 1.5 OR Plts less than 100 x 109/L: Delay one week. If CrCl is greater than or equal to 50 mL/minute, give as ordered. If CrCl less than 50 mL/minute, hold chemotherapy and contact prescriber. If AST/ALT less than or equal to 1.5 x ULN and Alk Phos is less than 1.5 x ULN and bilirubin is WLN: Give as ordered. If AST/ALT greater than 1.5 to 5 x ULN AND Alk Phos 1.5 to 5 x ULN OR bilirubin ULN to 1.5 x ULN: Administer 75% of vinorelbine dose. If AST/ALT greater than 5 x ULN AND Alk Phos greater than 5 x ULN OR bilirubin greater than 1.5 x ULN: HOLD treatment. If vinorelbine held for hepatic toxicity, repeat liver function tests weekly. Once recovered, dose vinorelbine at 75%.</value>
<value>If ANC is greater than or equal to 1.5 AND Plts are greater than or equal to 100 x 109/L: Give as ordered. If ANC is less than 1.5 OR Plts are less than 100 x 109/L: Delay 1 week. If calculated CrCl is greater than or equal to 50 mL/minute: give chemotherapy as ordered. If calculated CrCl is less than 50 mL/minute: Delay 1 week.</value>
<value>If ANC greater than or equal to 1.5 AND Plts greater than or equal to 100 x 109/L: Give as ordered. If ANC less than 1.5 OR Plts less than 100 x 109/L: Delay one week. If CrCl is greater than or equal to 50 mL/minute: Give as ordered. If CrCl less than 50 mL/minute: Contact physician.</value>
<value>If ANC is greater than or equal to 1.5 AND Plts greater than or equal to 100 x 109/L AND Creatinine Clearnace is greater than or equal to 45 mL/minute: Give as ordered. If ANC is less than 1.5 OR Plts are less than 100 x 109/L OR Creatinine Clearance is less than 45 mL/minute: Delay 1 week. </value>
<value>If ANC is greater than or equal to 1.5 AND Plts greater than or equal to 100 x 109/L: Give as ordered. If ANC is less than 1.5 OR Plts are less than 100 x 109/L: Contact physician. If Creatinine Clearance is greater than or equal to 50 mL/minute: Give as ordered. If Creatinine Clearance is less than 50 mL/minute: Contact physician.  </value>
<value>DAY 8. If ANC is greater than or equal to 1 AND Plts greater than or equal to 100 x 109/L: Give as ordered. If ANC is less than 1 OR Plts are less than 100 x 109/L: Contact physician. If Creatinine Clearance is greater than or equal to 50 mL/minute: Give as ordered. If Creatinine Clearance is less than 50 mL/minute: Contact physician.  </value>
<value>If ANC is greater than or equal to 1.5 AND Plts are greater than or equal to 100 x 109/L: Give as ordered. If ANC is less than 1.5 OR Plts are less than 100 x 109/L: Delay 1 week. If Creatinine Clearance is greater than or equal to 50 mL/minute: Give as ordered. If Creatinine Clearance is less than 50 mL/minute: Contact physician.</value>
<value>If ANC is greater than or equal to 1.5 AND Plts are greater than or equal to 100 x 109/L: Give as ordered. If ANC is less than 1.5 OR Plts are less than 100 x 109/L: Contact physician. If Creatinine Clearance is greater than or equal to 50 mL/minute: Give as ordered. If Creatinine Clearance is less than 50 mL/minute: Contact physician.</value>
</additionalnotes><population><value>Adjuvant Vinorelbine/CISplatin (every 28 days). Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer</value>
<value>Adjuvant Vinorelbine/CISplatin (every 21 days). Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer</value>
<value>Pemetrexed/CISplatin. Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer</value>
<value>Vinorelbine / CISplatin. Advanced NSCLC</value>
<value>CISplatin &amp; Vinorelbine with CONCURRENT RT. Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer</value>
<value>Gemcitabine / CISplatin. Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer</value>
<value>CISplatin/etoposide (po). Small Cell Lung Cancer</value>
<value>CISplatin/etoposide (IV). Small Cell Lung Cancer.</value>
<value>Pemetrexed / CISplatin. Mesothelioma.</value>
<value>Etoposide (Days 1-5)/CISplatin (Days 1 &amp; 8) with concurrent RT. Pancoast Tumor</value>
<value>DOXOrubicin/CISplatin/cyclophosphamide (PAC). Thymic Malignancy</value>
<value>CISplatin/DOXOrubicin/vinCRIStine/cyclophosphamide. Thymoma</value>
</population><indicationprn><value></value>
</indicationprn><backgroundinformation><value>http://intraweb01.albertahealthservices.ca/Pharmacy/AHS_FORMULARY/search_details.aspx?id=3356</value>
</backgroundinformation><prninformation><value></value>
</prninformation><ahsformularystatus><value>Formulary.</value>
</ahsformularystatus><ahfsname><value>Antineoplastic Agents</value>
</ahfsname><highalert><value>YES</value>
</highalert><maximumprndose><value>YES</value>
</maximumprndose></drug>