<?xml version="1.0"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../../web/xslt/drug-table.xslt"?><drug name = "dexamethasone inj VIAL">
<dose><value>4</value>
<value>6</value>
<value>1</value>
<value>2</value>
<value>10</value>
<value>20</value>
<value>8</value>
<value>12</value>
</dose><route><value>IM</value>
<value>INTRA-ARTICULAR</value>
<value>IV</value>
</route><form><value>inj VIAL</value>
</form><drugname><value>dexamethasone inj VIAL</value>
</drugname><strength><value>10 mg/mL</value>
<value>4 mg/mL</value>
</strength><frequency><value>Q6H</value>
<value>Q12H</value>
<value>ONCE </value>
<value>ONCE</value>
<value>BID</value>
<value>DAILY</value>
</frequency><instruction><value>for 4 doses.</value>
<value>DAY -1. BID for 3 days, starting the evening of chemotherapy. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 1 of 21. Administer 30 minutes prior to PACLitaxel.</value>
<value>DAY -1. Administer pre-chemotherapy. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 1. If oral anti-emetics have not been taken by patient as instructed, administer 30 to 60 minutes pre-chemotherapy. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 1. PRN. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 8. If oral anti-emetics have not been taken by patient as instructed, administer 30 to 60 minutes pre-chemotherapy. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 8. PRN. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 15. If oral anti-emetics have not been taken by patient as instructed, administer 30 to 60 minutes pre-chemotherapy. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 15. PRN. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 22. If oral anti-emetics have not been taken by patient as instructed, administer 30 to 60 minutes pre-chemotherapy. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 22. PRN. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 1 of 21. If oral anti-emetics have not been taken by patient as instructed, administer 30 to 60 minutes pre-chemotherapy. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 1 of 21. PRN. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 8 of 21. If oral anti-emetics have not been taken by patient as instructed, administer 30 to 60 minutes pre-chemotherapy. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 8 of 21. PRN. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 8 of 21. If oral anti-emetics have not been taken by patient as instructed, administer 30 to 60 minutes pre-gemcitabine. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 8 of 21. PRN. May be administered by IV route.</value>
<value>DAY 8 of 21. If oral anti-emetic has not been taken by patient as instructed, administer 30 to 60 minutes pre-gemcitabine. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 1 of 21. If oral anti-emetic has not been taken by patient as instructed, administer 30 to 60 minutes pre-gemcitabine. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 1 of 21. PRN. May be administered by IV route.</value>
<value>DAY 1 of 21. Administer 30 minutes prior to DOCEtaxel, if oral dexamethasone premedication has not been taken. </value>
<value>DAY 1 of 7. Administer 30 minutes prior to PACLitaxel.</value>
<value>DAYS 1, 2 &amp; 3 of 21. If oral anti-emetics have not been taken by patient as instructed, administer 30 to 60 minutes pre-chemotherapy. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAYS 1, 2 &amp; 3 of 21. PRN. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 1 of 28. If oral anti-emetics have not been taken by patient as instructed, administer 30 to 60 minutes pre-chemotherapy. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 1 of 28. PRN. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAYS 2, 3, 4 &amp; 5 of 28. If oral dexamethasone has not been taken by patient as instructed, administer 30 to 60 minutes pre-chemotherapy. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAYS 2, 3, 4 &amp; 5 of 28. PRN. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 8 of 28. If oral anti-emetics have not been taken by patient as instructed, administer 30 to 60 minutes pre-chemotherapy. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 8 of 28. PRN. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 1 of 21. If aprepitant was prescribed and not taken by patient as instructed, administer PRN. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 1 of 21. Administer prior to chemotherapy.</value>
<value>DAY 4 of 21. Administer pre-chemotherapy.</value>
<value>DAY 1 of 21. If oral dexamethasone has not been taken by patient as instructed, administer 30 minutes prior to DOCEtaxel.</value>
<value>DAY 1 of 21. May be administered by PO route.</value>
</instruction><volume><value>1 mL</value>
<value>10 mL</value>
<value>5 mL</value>
</volume><units><value>mg</value>
</units><additionalnotes></additionalnotes><population><value>PACLitaxel / CARBOplatin. Advanced / Metastatic Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer</value>
<value>Adjuvant Vinorelbine/CISplatin (every 28 days). Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer</value>
<value>Adjuvant Vinorelbine/CISplatin (every 21 days). Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer</value>
<value>Adjuvant PACLitaxel/CARBOplatin. Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer</value>
<value>Vinorelbine / CISplatin. Advanced NSCLC</value>
<value>Vinorelbine / CARBOplatin. Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer (Advanced Stage)</value>
<value>CISplatin &amp; Vinorelbine with CONCURRENT RT. Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer</value>
<value>Gemcitabine / CARBOplatin. Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer</value>
<value>Gemcitabine / CISplatin. Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer</value>
<value>Gemcitabine. Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer</value>
<value>DOCEtaxel. Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer</value>
<value>PACLitaxel/CARBOplatin (Weekly) and concurrent RT. Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer.</value>
<value>cyclophosphamide, DOXOrubicin, vinCRIStine (CAV). Small Cell Lung Cancer.</value>
<value>CISplatin/etoposide (po). Small Cell Lung Cancer</value>
<value>CISplatin/etoposide (IV). Small Cell Lung Cancer.</value>
<value>Carboplatin/Etoposide (IV). Small Cell Lung Cancer.</value>
<value>CARBOplatin/Etoposide (IV/po). Small Cell Lung Cancer</value>
<value>Etoposide (Days 1-5)/CISplatin (Days 1 &amp; 8) with concurrent RT. Pancoast Tumor</value>
<value>DOXOrubicin/CISplatin/cyclophosphamide (PAC). Thymic Malignancy</value>
<value>Vinorelbine and CARBOplatin with CONCURRENT RT. Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer.</value>
<value>CISplatin/DOXOrubicin/vinCRIStine/cyclophosphamide. Thymoma</value>
<value>Fluorouracil, Epirubicin, Cyclophosphamide (FEC) followed by DOCEtaxel. Breast Cancer (NEOADJUVANT Treatment).</value>
<value>Fluorouracil, Epirubicin, Cyclophosphamide (FEC) followed by DOCEtaxel &amp; Trastuzumab</value>
<value>Fluorouracil, Epirubicin, Cyclophosphamide (FEC) followed by DOCEtaxel and Trastuzumab. Breast Cancer (NEOADJUVANT Treatment).</value>
<value>DOXOrubicin, Cyclophosphamide (AC) followed by DOCEtaxel. Breast Cancer (NEOADJUVANT Treatment).</value>
<value>DOXOrubicin, Cyclophosphamide (AC) followed by DOCEtaxel and Trastuzumab. Breast Cancer (NEOADJUVANT Treatment).</value>
<value>DOXOrubicin, Cyclophosphamide (AC) followed by PACLitaxel (weekly) and Trastuzumab. Breast Cancer (NEOADJUVANT Treatment).</value>
</population><indicationprn><value>Nausea</value>
</indicationprn><backgroundinformation></backgroundinformation><prninformation><value>YES</value>
</prninformation><ahsformularystatus><value>Formulary.</value>
<value>Formulary with Usage guidelines.</value>
</ahsformularystatus><ahfsname><value>Adrenals</value>
</ahfsname><highalert></highalert><maximumprndose></maximumprndose><din><value>00874582</value>
<value>02204274</value>
<value>02204266</value>
</din></drug>