<?xml version="1.0"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../../web/xslt/drug-table.xslt"?><drug name = "ibutilide inj VIAL>
<dose><value>1</value>
<value>10</value>
<value>0.5</value>
<value>5</value>
</dose><route><value>IV</value>
</route><form><value>inj VIAL</value>
</form><drugname><value>ibutilide inj VIAL</value>
</drugname><strength><value>0.1 mg/mL</value>
</strength><frequency><value>ONCE</value>
</frequency><instruction><value>Administer intravenously over 10 minutes.</value>
</instruction><volume><value>10 mL</value>
</volume><units><value>mg</value>
<value>mcg/kg</value>
</units><additionalnotes><value>Supraventricular Tachyarrythmias in patients weighing 60 kg or more: if arrythmia does not erminate within 10 minutes after the end of the initial infusion, a second equal dose may be administered 10 minutes after completion of the initial dose.  Recommended to administer 1 to 2.5 g magnesium sulfate intravenously prior to ibutilide dosing to prevent Torsades de Pointes VT.  Ensure serum potassium is greater than 3.7 mmol/L.</value>
<value>Supraventricular Tachyarrythmias in patients weighing less than 60 kg: if arrythmia does not erminate within 10 minutes after the end of the initial infusion, a second equal dose may be administered 10 minutes after completion of the initial dose.  Recommended to administer 1 to 2.5 g magnesium sulfate intravenously prior to ibutilide dosing to prevent Torsades de Pointes VT.  Ensure serum potassium is greater than 3.7 mmol/L.</value>
<value>Post-cardiac surgery in patients weighing 60 kg or more: if arrythmia does not erminate within 10 minutes after the end of the initial infusion, a second equal dose may be administered 10 minutes after completion of the initial dose.  Recommended to administer 1 to 2.5 g magnesium sulfate intravenously prior to ibutilide dosing to prevent Torsades de Pointes VT.  Ensure serum potassium is greater than 3.7 mmol/L.</value>
<value>Post-cardiac surgery in patients weighing less than 60 kg: if arrythmia does not erminate within 10 minutes after the end of the initial infusion, a second equal dose may be administered 10 minutes after completion of the initial dose.  Recommended to administer 1 to 2.5 g magnesium sulfate intravenously prior to ibutilide dosing to prevent Torsades de Pointes VT.  Ensure serum potassium is greater than 3.7 mmol/L.</value>
</additionalnotes><population><value>ADULT. Safety and efficacy in patients with renal/hepatic failure not established. Although dosing adjustments are unlikely, it is recommended patient with abnormal liver function undergo continuous ECG monitoring beyond the usual 4 hour period seen with other patients.</value>
</population><indicationprn><value></value>
</indicationprn><backgroundinformation><value></value>
</backgroundinformation><prninformation><value></value>
</prninformation><ahsformularystatus><value>Formulary with Restrictions.</value>
</ahsformularystatus><ahfsname><value>Cardiac Drugs, Antiarrhythmic Agents</value>
</ahfsname><highalert><value>YES</value>
</highalert><maximumprndose><value>YES</value>
</maximumprndose></drug>