<?xml version="1.0"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../../web/xslt/drug-table.xslt"?><drug name = "nicotine gum>
<dose><value>2</value>
<value>4</value>
</dose><route><value>BUCCAL</value>
</route><form><value>gum</value>
</form><drug><value>nicotine gum</value>
</drug><strength><value>2 mg</value>
<value>4 mg</value>
</strength><frequency><value>Q1H</value>
<value>Q2H</value>
<value>Q3H</value>
<value>Q4H</value>
<value>Q6H</value>
<value>Q8H</value>
</frequency><instruction><value>Chew gum piece slowly and intermittently for 30 minutes. </value>
</instruction><volume><value></value>
</volume><units><value>mg</value>
</units><additionalnotes><value>FIRST MONTH. Approximately one piece per hour is common for a pack a day smoker. Recommend 2 mg gum for patients with a score of 6 or less using the Fagerstrom nicotine tolerance scale.</value>
<value>SECOND MONTH. Recommend 2 mg gum for patients with a score of 6 or less using the fagerstrom nicotine tolerance scale.</value>
<value>THIRD MONTH. Recommend 2 mg gum for patients with a score of 6 or less using the fagerstrom nicotine tolerance scale.</value>
<value>FIRST MONTH. Approximately one piece per hour is common for a pack a day smoker. Recommend 4 mg gum for patients with a score of 7 or greater using the Fagerstrom nicotine tolerance scale OR for patients who have cravings while using the 2 mg strength gum.</value>
<value>SECOND MONTH. Recommend 4 mg gum for patients with a score of 7 or greater using the fagerstrom nicotine tolerance scale or for patients who have cravings while using the 2 mg strength gum.</value>
<value>THIRD MONTH. Recommend 4 mg gum for patients with a score of 7 or greater using the fagerstrom nicotine tolerance scale or for patients who have cravings while using the 2 mg strength gum.</value>
</additionalnotes><population><value></value>
</population><indicationprn><value>Smoking cessation</value>
</indicationprn><backgroundinformation><value>Patient should not exceed 20 pieces of gum per day during first month.</value>
<value></value>
</backgroundinformation><prninformation><value>YES</value>
</prninformation><ahsformularystatus><value>Formulary.</value>
</ahsformularystatus><ahfsname><value>Autonomic Drugs, Miscellaneous</value>
</ahfsname><highalert><value></value>
</highalert><maximumprndose><value></value>
</maximumprndose></drug>