<?xml version="1.0"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../../web/xslt/drug-table.xslt"?><drug name = "ondansetron inj VIAL">
<dose><value>4</value>
<value>8</value>
<value>16</value>
</dose><route><value>IM</value>
<value>IV</value>
<value>SC</value>
</route><form><value>inj VIAL</value>
</form><drugname><value>ondansetron inj VIAL</value>
</drugname><strength><value>2 mg/mL</value>
</strength><frequency><value>Q3H</value>
<value>Q4H</value>
<value>ONCE</value>
<value>DAILY</value>
<value>Q8H</value>
</frequency><instruction><value>PRE-OP Induction</value>
<value>Administer 30 minutes pre-chemotherapy.</value>
<value>for 3 doses POST_CHEMOTHERAPY.</value>
<value>DAY 1 of 21. If oral anti-emetics have not been taken by patient as instructed, administer 30 to 60 minutes pre-chemotherapy. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 1 of 21. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 8 of 21. If oral anti-emetics have not been taken by patient as instructed, administer 30 to 60 minutes pre-chemotherapy. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 8 of 21. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 1 of 21. If oral anti-emetic has not been taken by patient as instructed, administer 30 to 60 minutes pre-CARBOplatin. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 1 of 21. If oral ondansetron has not been taken by patient as instructed, administer 30 to 60 minutes pre-chemotherapy. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 1 of 21. If oral antiemetics have not been taken by patient as instructed, administer 30 to 60 minutes pre-chemotherapy. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 1 of 21. If oral anti-emetic has not been taken by patient as instructed, administer 30 to 60 minutes pre-chemotherapy. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 1 of 7. If oral ondansetron has not been taken by patient as instructed, administer 30 minutes pre-PACLitaxel. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 1 of 7. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 1 of 21. If oral anti-emetics have not been taken by patient as instructed, administer 30 to 60 minutes pre-chemotherapy. May be administered by IV route.</value>
<value>DAYS 1, 2 &amp; 3 of 21. If oral anti-emetics have not been taken by patient as instructed, administer 30 to 60 minutes pre-chemotherapy. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAYS 1, 2 &amp; 3 of 21. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 1 of 28. If oral anti-emetics have not been taken by patient as instructed, administer 30 to 60 minutes pre-chemotherapy. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 1 of 28. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 8 of 28. If oral anti-emetics have not been taken by patient as instructed, administer 30 to 60 minutes pre-chemotherapy. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 8 of 28. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 1 of 21. If aprepitant was prescribed and not taken by patient as instructed, administer PRN nausea. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 1 of 21. Administer pre-chemotherapy.</value>
<value>DAY 4 of 21. Administer pre-chemotherapy.</value>
<value>DAY 1 of 21. for nausea. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 1. If oral anti-emetics have not been taken by patient as instructed, administer 30 to 60 minutes pre-chemotherapy. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 1. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 8. If oral anti-emetics have not been taken by patient as instructed, administer 30 to 60 minutes pre-chemotherapy. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 8. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 15. If oral anti-emetics have not been taken by patient as instructed, administer 30 to 60 minutes pre-chemotherapy. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 15. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 22. If oral anti-emetics have not been taken by patient as instructed, administer 30 to 60 minutes pre-chemotherapy. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 22. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY -1. Administer pre-chemotherapy. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY -1. For 3 days, starting the evening of chemotherapy. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 2. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 0. Administer 30 minutes pre-transplant. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 0. Administer 60 minutes pre-transplant. May be administered by PO route.</value>
</instruction><volume><value>2 mL</value>
<value>20 mL</value>
<value>4 mL</value>
</volume><units><value>mg</value>
</units><additionalnotes><value>Initiate order following completion of ondansetron 8 mg PO/IV Q8h x 3 days.</value>
</additionalnotes><population><value>Adjuvant Vinorelbine/CISplatin (every 21 days). Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer</value>
<value>Adjuvant PACLitaxel/CARBOplatin. Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer</value>
<value>Pemetrexed/CISplatin. Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer</value>
<value>Pemetrexed / CARBOplatin. Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer</value>
<value>Vinorelbine / CISplatin. Advanced NSCLC</value>
<value>Vinorelbine / CARBOplatin. Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer (Advanced Stage)</value>
<value>CISplatin &amp; Vinorelbine with CONCURRENT RT. Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer</value>
<value>PACLitaxel / CARBOplatin. Advanced / Metastatic Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer</value>
<value>Gemcitabine / CARBOplatin. Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer</value>
<value>Gemcitabine / CISplatin. Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer</value>
<value>PACLitaxel/CARBOplatin (Weekly) and concurrent RT. Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer.</value>
<value>cyclophosphamide, DOXOrubicin, vinCRIStine (CAV). Small Cell Lung Cancer.</value>
<value>CISplatin/etoposide (po). Small Cell Lung Cancer</value>
<value>CISplatin/etoposide (IV). Small Cell Lung Cancer.</value>
<value>Carboplatin/Etoposide (IV). Small Cell Lung Cancer.</value>
<value>CARBOplatin/Etoposide (IV/po). Small Cell Lung Cancer</value>
<value>Pemetrexed / CARBOplatin. Mesothelioma</value>
<value>Pemetrexed / CISplatin. Mesothelioma.</value>
<value>Etoposide (Days 1-5)/CISplatin (Days 1 &amp; 8) with concurrent RT. Pancoast Tumor</value>
<value>DOXOrubicin/CISplatin/cyclophosphamide (PAC). Thymic Malignancy</value>
<value>Vinorelbine and CARBOplatin with CONCURRENT RT. Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer.</value>
<value>CISplatin/DOXOrubicin/vinCRIStine/cyclophosphamide. Thymoma</value>
<value>Fluorouracil, Epirubicin, Cyclophosphamide (FEC) followed by DOCEtaxel. Breast Cancer (NEOADJUVANT Treatment).</value>
<value>Fluorouracil, Epirubicin, Cyclophosphamide (FEC) followed by DOCEtaxel &amp; Trastuzumab</value>
<value>DOXOrubicin, Cyclophosphamide (AC) followed by DOCEtaxel. Breast Cancer (NEOADJUVANT Treatment).</value>
<value>DOXOrubicin, Cyclophosphamide (AC) followed by DOCEtaxel and Trastuzumab. Breast Cancer (NEOADJUVANT Treatment).</value>
<value>DOXOrubicin, Cyclophosphamide (AC) followed by PACLitaxel (weekly) and Trastuzumab. Breast Cancer (NEOADJUVANT Treatment).</value>
<value>Adjuvant Vinorelbine/CISplatin (every 28 days). Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer</value>
</population><indicationprn><value>Nausea</value>
</indicationprn><backgroundinformation></backgroundinformation><prninformation><value>YES</value>
</prninformation><ahsformularystatus><value>Formulary with Usage guidelines, therapeutic interchange.</value>
</ahsformularystatus><ahfsname><value>Antiemetics, 5-HT3 Receptor Antagonists</value>
</ahfsname><highalert></highalert><maximumprndose></maximumprndose><din><value>02274418</value>
<value>02390051</value>
</din></drug>