<?xml version="1.0"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../../web/xslt/drug-table.xslt"?><drug name = "oxaliplatin inj VIAL>
<dose><value>85</value>
<value>130</value>
<value>100</value>
</dose><route><value>IV</value>
</route><form><value>inj VIAL</value>
</form><drugname><value>oxaliplatin inj VIAL</value>
</drugname><strength><value>100 mg</value>
<value>5 mg/mL</value>
<value>50 mg</value>
</strength><frequency><value>ONCE</value>
</frequency><instruction><value>Administer dose over 2 hours.</value>
<value>Administer dose over 6 hours.</value>
<value>Administer dose over 2 to 4 hours.</value>
</instruction><volume><value></value>
<value>10 mL</value>
<value>20 mL</value>
</volume><units><value>mg/m2</value>
</units><additionalnotes><value>Colorectal cancer. Doses less than 60 mg provided in 100 mL D5W, doses 60 to 120 mg provided in 250 mL D5W and doses greater than 120 mg provided in D5W 500 mL.</value>
<value>Colorectal cancer. Dose administered over 6 hours if patient has experienced pharyngo-laryngeal dysesthesia in prior infusions. Doses less than 60 mg provided in 100 mL D5W, doses 60 to 120 mg provided in 250 mL D5W and doses greater than 120 mg provided in D5W 500 mL.</value>
<value>Colorectal cancer. Extend administration time to 4 hours to reduce discomfort in the infusion arm. Doses less than 60 mg provided in 100 mL D5W, doses 60 to 120 mg provided in 250 mL D5W and doses greater than 120 mg provided in D5W 500 mL.</value>
<value>Colorectal cancer. Doses up to 120 mg provided in 250 mL D5W and doses greater than 120 mg provided in D5W 500 mL.</value>
<value>Rectal cancer. Doses less than 60 mg provided in 100 mL D5W, doses 60 to 120 mg provided in 250 mL D5W and doses greater than 120 mg provided in D5W 500 mL.</value>
<value>Rectal cancer. Dose administered over 6 hours if patient has experienced pharyngo-laryngeal dysesthesia in prior infusions. Doses less than 60 mg provided in 100 mL D5W, doses 60 to 120 mg provided in 250 mL D5W and doses greater than 120 mg provided in D5W 500 mL.</value>
<value>Rectal cancer. Extend administration time to 4 hours to reduce discomfort in the infusion arm. Doses less than 60 mg provided in 100 mL D5W, doses 60 to 120 mg provided in 250 mL D5W and doses greater than 120 mg provided in D5W 500 mL.</value>
<value>Esophagogastric/Gastric/Esophagus cancer. Extend administration time to 4 hours to reduce discomfort in the infusion arm. Doses less than 60 mg provided in 100 mL D5W, doses 60 to 120 mg provided in 250 mL D5W and doses greater than 120 mg provided in D5W 500 mL.</value>
<value>Esophagogastric/Gastric/Esophagus cancer. Dose administered over 6 hours if patient has experienced pharyngo-laryngeal dysesthesia in prior infusions. Doses less than 60 mg provided in 100 mL D5W, doses 60 to 120 mg provided in 250 mL D5W and doses greater than 120 mg provided in D5W 500 mL.</value>
<value>Esophageal cancer. Doses up to 120 mg provided in 250 mL D5W and doses greater than 120 mg provided in D5W 500 mL.</value>
<value>Esophageal cancer. Dose administered over 6 hours if patient has experienced pharyngo-laryngeal dysesthesia in prior infusions. Doses up to 120 mg provided in 250 mL D5W and doses greater than 120 mg provided in D5W 500 mL.</value>
<value>Metastatic Pancreatic cancer. Doses less than 60 mg provided in 100 mL D5W, doses 60 to 120 mg provided in 250 mL D5W and doses greater than 120 mg provided in D5W 500 mL.</value>
<value>Metastatic Pancreatic cancer. Dose administered over 6 hours if patient has experienced pharyngo-laryngeal dysesthesia in prior infusions. Doses less than 60 mg provided in 100 mL D5W, doses 60 to 120 mg provided in 250 mL D5W and doses greater than 120 mg provided in D5W 500 mL.</value>
<value>Advanced Pancreatic cancer. Doses less than 60 mg provided in 100 mL D5W, doses 60 to 120 mg provided in 250 mL D5W and doses greater than 120 mg provided in D5W 500 mL.</value>
<value>Advanced Pancreatic cancer. Dose administered over 6 hours if patient has experienced pharyngo-laryngeal dysesthesia in prior infusions. Doses less than 60 mg provided in 100 mL D5W, doses 60 to 120 mg provided in 250 mL D5W and doses greater than 120 mg provided in D5W 500 mL.</value>
<value>Metastatic Coloractal cancer. Doses up to 120 mg provided in 250 mL D5W and doses greater than 120 mg provided in D5W 500 mL.</value>
<value>Metastatic Colorectal cancer. Dose administered over 6 hours if patient has experienced pharyngo-laryngeal dysesthesia in prior infusions. Doses up to 120 mg provided in 250 mL D5W and doses greater than 120 mg provided in D5W 500 mL.</value>
</additionalnotes><population><value>ADULT</value>
</population><indicationprn><value></value>
</indicationprn><backgroundinformation><value>http://intraweb01.albertahealthservices.ca/Pharmacy/AHS_FORMULARY/search_details.aspx?id=3429</value>
<value>http://intraweb01.albertahealthservices.ca/Pharmacy/AHS_FORMULARY/search_details.aspx?id=3426</value>
<value>http://intraweb01.albertahealthservices.ca/Pharmacy/AHS_FORMULARY/search_details.aspx?id=3428</value>
</backgroundinformation><prninformation><value></value>
</prninformation><ahsformularystatus><value>Formulary with Usage guidelines.</value>
</ahsformularystatus><ahfsname><value>Antineoplastic Agents</value>
</ahfsname><highalert><value>YES</value>
</highalert><maximumprndose><value>YES</value>
</maximumprndose></drug>