<?xml version="1.0"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../../web/xslt/drug-table.xslt"?><drug name = "praziquantel tab>
<dose><value>450</value>
<value>600</value>
<value>750</value>
<value>900</value>
<value>1050</value>
<value>1200</value>
<value>1350</value>
<value>1500</value>
<value>1650</value>
<value>20</value>
<value>1800</value>
<value>25</value>
</dose><route><value>PO</value>
</route><form><value>tab</value>
</form><drug><value>praziquantel tab</value>
</drug><strength><value>600 mg</value>
</strength><frequency><value>Q4H</value>
</frequency><instruction><value>for 3 doses.</value>
</instruction><volume><value></value>
</volume><units><value>mg</value>
<value>mg/kg</value>
</units><additionalnotes><value>Recommended dosing for schistosomiasis in patients weighting 20 to 25 kg.</value>
<value>Recommended dosing for schistosomiasis in patients weighting 26 to 33 kg.</value>
<value>Recommended dosing for schistosomiasis in patients weighting 34 to 41 kg.</value>
<value>Recommended dosing for schistosomiasis in patients weighting 42 to 48 kg.</value>
<value>Recommended dosing for schistosomiasis in patients weighting 49 to 56 kg.</value>
<value>Recommended dosing for schistosomiasis in patients weighting 57 to 63 kg.</value>
<value>Recommended dosing for schistosomiasis in patients weighting 64 to 70 kg.</value>
<value>Recommended dosing for schistosomiasis in patients weighting 71 to 78 kg.</value>
<value>Recommended dosing for schistosomiasis in patients weighting 79 to 86 kg.</value>
<value>Recommended dosing for schistosomiasis.</value>
<value>Recommended dosing for clonorchiasis and opisthorchiasis in patients weighting 22 to 26 kg.</value>
<value>Recommended dosing for clonorchiasis and opisthorchiasis in patients weighting 27 to 33 kg.</value>
<value>Recommended dosing for clonorchiasis and opisthorchiasis in patients weighting 34 to 38 kg.</value>
<value>Recommended dosing for clonorchiasis and opisthorchiasis in patients weighting 39 to 44 kg.</value>
<value>Recommended dosing for clonorchiasis and opisthorchiasis in patients weighting 45 to 50 kg.</value>
<value>Recommended dosing for clonorchiasis and opisthorchiasis in patients weighting 51 to 56 kg.</value>
<value>Recommended dosing for clonorchiasis and opisthorchiasis in patients weighting 57 to 62 kg.</value>
<value>Recommended dosing for clonorchiasis and opisthorchiasis in patients weighting 63 to 68 kg.</value>
<value>Recommended dosing for clonorchiasis and opisthorchiasis in patients weighting 69 to 75 kg.</value>
<value>Recommended dosing for clonorchiasis and opisthorchiasis.</value>
</additionalnotes><population><value></value>
</population><indicationprn><value></value>
</indicationprn><backgroundinformation><value>450 mg = 3/4 of one 600 mg tablet</value>
<value></value>
<value>750 mg = 1 &amp; 1/4 tablets of 600 mg.</value>
<value>900 mg = 1 &amp; 1/2 tablets of 600 mg.</value>
<value>1050 mg = 1 &amp; 3/4 tablets of 600 mg.</value>
<value>1200 mg = 2 tablets of 600 mg.</value>
<value>1350 mg = 2 &amp; 1/4 tablets of 600 mg.</value>
<value>1500 mg = 2 &amp; 1/2 tablets of 600 mg.</value>
<value>1650 mg = 2 &amp; 3/4 tablets of 600 mg.</value>
<value>1800 mg = 3 tablets of 600 mg.</value>
</backgroundinformation><prninformation><value></value>
</prninformation><ahsformularystatus><value>Formulary.</value>
</ahsformularystatus><ahfsname><value>Anthelmintics</value>
</ahfsname><highalert><value></value>
</highalert><maximumprndose><value></value>
</maximumprndose></drug>