<?xml version="1.0"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../../web/xslt/drug-table.xslt"?><drug name = "propofol inj VIAL">
<dose><value>0.3 - 4.5</value>
<value>0.3 - 3</value>
<value>10</value>
<value>0.3 - 5</value>
<value>0.5 - 5</value>
<value>1</value>
<value>0.5</value>
<value>5 - 50</value>
<value>250 - 1000</value>
<value>25 - 100</value>
<value></value>
</dose><route><value>IV</value>
</route><form><value>inj VIAL</value>
</form><drugname><value>propofol inj VIAL</value>
</drugname><strength><value>10 mg/mL</value>
</strength><frequency><value>CONTINUOUS</value>
<value>ONCE</value>
</frequency><instruction><value>Initial Dose: Start at lower dose for at least 5 minutes. Increase by increments of 0.3 to 0.6 mg/kg/hour over 5 to 10 minutes until desired level of sedation is reached. </value>
<value>Administer by continuous infusion; maintenance dose.</value>
<value>Administer by direct injection every 30 to 60 seconds until target sedation level achieved.</value>
<value>Initial Dose: Start at 0.3 mg/kg/hour for at least 5 minutes. Increase by increments of 0.3 to 0.6 mg/kg/hour over 5 to 10 minutes until desired level of sedation is reached. </value>
<value>Initial dose: Administer by direct injection over 1 to 2 minutes. Up to a MAXIMUM dose of 40 mg.</value>
<value>Maintenance Dose: Administer by direct injection. Up to a MAX dose of 20 mg administered every 45 seconds or longer.</value>
<value>Administer by continuous infusion. Titrate to desired clinical effect and minimal hypotension. A minimum period of 5 minutes between dosage adjustments to be allowed for peak drug effect.</value>
<value>Initial dose: Administer over 3 to 5 minutes.</value>
<value></value>
</instruction><volume><value>100 mL</value>
<value>20 mL</value>
<value>50 mL</value>
</volume><units><value>mg/kg/hour</value>
<value>mg</value>
<value>mg/kg</value>
<value>mcg/kg/minute</value>
</units><additionalnotes><value>AHS Provincial Adult Standard Concentration: 10 mg/mL</value>
<value></value>
</additionalnotes><population><value>ADULT sedation in critical care areas. Maximum rate should not exceed 5 mg/kg/hour, due to potential cardiac toxicity.</value>
<value>ADULT procedural sedation (55 years or less, ASA Class I or II). Maximum rate should not exceed 5 mg/kg/hour, due to potential cardiac toxicity. Maintenance infusion: 1.5 to 4.5 mg/kg/hour. Reduce dose and rate by 20 to 30% in geriactric, debilitated and/or ASA Class II or IV patients.</value>
<value>INFANTS / CHILDREN: Critical care sedation; patients older than 3 months. Propofol has been used safely in hemodynamically stable, non-acidotic patients older than 3 months of age, with a MAX mean dose of 4 mg/kg/hour, for a MAX duration of 24 hours, when judged to be the optimal therapy under the circumstances. </value>
<value>INFANTS / CHILDREN: Procedural sedation. MAXIMUM dose: 40 mg.</value>
<value>INFANTS / CHILDREN: Procedural Sedation.</value>
<value>ADULT sedation in critical care areas.</value>
<value>ADULT sedation during surgical or diagnostic procedures.</value>
<value></value>
</population><indicationprn><value></value>
<value>Sedation</value>
</indicationprn><backgroundinformation><value></value>
</backgroundinformation><prninformation><value></value>
<value>YES</value>
</prninformation><ahsformularystatus><value>Formulary.</value>
</ahsformularystatus><ahfsname><value>General Anesthetics</value>
</ahfsname><highalert><value>YES</value>
</highalert><maximumprndose><value>YES</value>
</maximumprndose></drug>