<?xml version="1.0"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="drug-table.xslt"?><drug name = "diphenhydrAMINE inj AMP">
<dose><value>10</value>
<value>12.5</value>
<value>25</value>
<value>50</value>
<value>100</value>
<value>25 - 50</value>
</dose>
<route><value>IM</value>
<value>IV</value>
</route>
<strength><value>50 mg/mL</value>
</strength>
<frequency><value>NOW</value>
<value>Q4H</value>
<value>Q6H</value>
<value>ONCE</value>
</frequency>
<instruction><value>DAY 0. Administer 30 to 60 minutes pre-transplant. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 1 of 21. If oral diphenhydrAMINE has not been taken by patient as instructed, administer 30 minutes pre-PACLitaxel. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 1 of 21. PRN. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 1 of 21. PRN sensitivity reaction. (and refer to Cancer Care Nursing Management of Infusion-Related Hypersensitivity Reactions Policy and Procedures.</value>
<value>DAY 1 of 21. Administer pre-CARBOplatin if lifetime exposure to CARBOplatin is greater than 6 cycles..</value>
<value>DAY 1 of 21. Administer pre-CARBOplatin PRN.</value>
<value>DAY 1 of 21. PRN sensitivity reaction. (and refer to Cancer Care Nursing Management of Infusion-Related Hypersensitivity Reactions Policy and Procedures.)</value>
<value>DAY 1 of 21. PRN hypersensitivity reaction. (and refer to Cancer Care Nursing Management of Infusion-Related and Hypersensitivity Reactions Policy and Procedures.)</value>
<value>DAY 1 of 7. If oral diphenhydrAMINE has not been taken by patient as instructed, administer 30 minutes pre-PACLitaxel. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 1 of 7. PRN. May be administered by PO route.</value>
<value>DAY 1 of 7. PRN hypersensitivity reaction. (and refer to Cancer Care Nursing Management of Infusion-Related Hypersensitivity Reactions Policy and Procedures.)</value>
<value>DAY 1 of 21. PRN hypersensitivity reaction. (and refer to CancerControl Nursing Management of Infusion-Related and Hypersensitivity Reactions Policy and Procedures).</value>
<value>DAY 1 of 21. for hypersensitivity reaction. (and refer to CancerControl Nursing Management of Infusion-Related and Hypersensitivity Reactions Policy and Procedures).</value>
</instruction>
<volume><value>1 mL</value>
</volume>
<units><value>mg</value>
</units>
<Population><value>Adjuvant PACLitaxel/CARBOplatin. Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer</value>
<value>Pemetrexed / CARBOplatin. Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer</value>
<value>Vinorelbine / CARBOplatin. Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer (Advanced Stage)</value>
<value>PACLitaxel / CARBOplatin. Advanced / Metastatic Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer</value>
<value>DOCEtaxel. Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer</value>
<value>PACLitaxel/CARBOplatin (Weekly) and concurrent RT. Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer.</value>
<value>Carboplatin/Etoposide (IV). Small Cell Lung Cancer.</value>
<value>CARBOplatin/Etoposide (IV/po). Small Cell Lung Cancer</value>
<value>Pemetrexed / CARBOplatin. Mesothelioma</value>
<value>Fluorouracil, Epirubicin, Cyclophosphamide (FEC) followed by DOCEtaxel. Breast Cancer (NEOADJUVANT Treatment).</value>
<value>Fluorouracil, Epirubicin, Cyclophosphamide (FEC) followed by DOCEtaxel &amp; Trastuzumab</value>
<value>Fluorouracil, Epirubicin, Cyclophosphamide (FEC) followed by DOCEtaxel and Trastuzumab. Breast Cancer (NEOADJUVANT Treatment).</value>
<value>DOXOrubicin, Cyclophosphamide (AC) followed by DOCEtaxel. Breast Cancer (NEOADJUVANT Treatment).</value>
<value>DOXOrubicin, Cyclophosphamide (AC) followed by DOCEtaxel and Trastuzumab. Breast Cancer (NEOADJUVANT Treatment).</value>
</Population>
<IndicationPRN></IndicationPRN>
<AdditionalNotes></AdditionalNotes>
<BackgroundInformation></BackgroundInformation>
<PRNInformation><value>YES</value>
</PRNInformation>
<AHSFormularyStatus></AHSFormularyStatus>
<HighAlert></HighAlert>
</drug>