<?xml version="1.0"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="drug-table.xslt"?><drug name = "etoposide inj VIAL">
<dose><value>100</value>
<value>50</value>
</dose>
<route><value>IV</value>
</route>
<strength><value>20 mg/mL</value>
</strength>
<frequency><value>ONCE</value>
<value>DAILY</value>
</frequency>
<instruction><value>DAY 1 of 21. Administer dose in the following volume and at the corrsponding rate: a) Dilute dose in 500 mL - 0.9% sodium chloride (for doses less than or equal to 200 mg) and administer over 1 hour. b) Dilute dose in 1000 mL - 0.9% sodium chloride (for doses greater than 200 mg) and administer over 1.5 to 2 hours. </value>
<value>DAYS 1, 2 &amp; 3 of 21. DAILY for 3 days. Administer dose in the following volume and at the corrsponding rate DAILY for 3 days: a) Dilute dose in 500 mL - 0.9% sodium chloride (for doses less than or equal to 200 mg) and administer over 1 hour. b) Dilute dose in 1000 mL - 0.9% sodium chloride (for doses greater than 200 mg) and administer over 1.5 to 2 hours. </value>
<value>DAYS 1, 2 &amp; 3 of 21. DAILY for 3 days. Administer dose in the following volume and at the corrsponding rate: a) Dilute dose in 500 mL - 0.9% sodium chloride (for doses less than or equal to 200 mg) and administer over 1 hour. b) Dilute dose in 1000 mL - 0.9% sodium chloride (for doses greater than 200 mg) and administer over 1.5 to 2 hours. </value>
<value>DAY 1 of 28. Administer dose diluted in 500 mL - 0.9% sodium chloride over 1 hour on DAY 1 post-CISplatin. </value>
<value>DAYS 2, 3, 4 &amp; 5 of 28. DAILY for 4 days. Administer dose diluted in 500 mL - 0.9% sodium chloride over 1 hour on DAYS 2, 3, 4 and 5. </value>
<value>DAYS 2, 3, 4 &amp; 5 of 28. DAILY  for 4 days. Administer dose diluted in 500 mL - 0.9% sodium chloride over 1 hour on DAYS 2, 3, 4 and 5. </value>
</instruction>
<volume><value>25 mL</value>
<value>5 mL</value>
</volume>
<units><value>mg/m2</value>
<value>mg/m2/day</value>
</units>
<Population><value>CISplatin/etoposide (po). Small Cell Lung Cancer</value>
<value>CISplatin/etoposide (IV). Small Cell Lung Cancer.</value>
<value>Carboplatin/Etoposide (IV). Small Cell Lung Cancer.</value>
<value>CARBOplatin/Etoposide (IV/po). Small Cell Lung Cancer</value>
<value>Etoposide (Days 1-5)/CISplatin (Days 1 &amp; 8) with concurrent RT. Pancoast Tumor</value>
</Population>
<IndicationPRN></IndicationPRN>
<AdditionalNotes><value>If ANC greater than or equal to 1.5 AND Plts greater than or equal to 100 x 109/L: Give as ordered. If ANC less than 1.5 OR Plts less than 100 x 109/L: Delay one week. If CrCl is greater than or equal to 50 mL/minute: Give as ordered. If CrCl less than 50 mL/minute: Contact physician.</value>
<value>If ANC greater than or equal to 1.5 AND Plts greater than or equal to 100 x 109/L: Give as ordered. If ANC less than 1.5 OR Plts less than 100 x 109/L: Delay one week.</value>
<value>If ANC is greater than or equal to 1.5 AND Plts greater than or equal to 100 x 109/L: Give as ordered. If ANC is less than 1.5 OR Plts are less than 100 x 109/L: Contact physician. If Creatinine Clearance is greater than or equal to 50 mL/minute: Give as ordered. If Creatinine Clearance is less than 50 mL/minute: Contact physician.  </value>
</AdditionalNotes>
<BackgroundInformation><value>http://intraweb01.albertahealthservices.ca/Pharmacy/AHS_FORMULARY/search_details.aspx?id=3388</value>
</BackgroundInformation>
<PRNInformation></PRNInformation>
<AHSFormularyStatus><value>Formulary.</value>
</AHSFormularyStatus>
<AHFSName><value>Antineoplastic Agents</value>
</AHFSName>
<HighAlert><value>YES</value>
</HighAlert>
</drug>